dynamicoxygen.com 2012-10-15

# DynamicOxygen - The New Wave in Search Targeting!

  |  | | Company Overview  
  
---|---  
| Product Overview  
  
| Investor Relations  
  
| Careers  
  
| Press Resources  
  
| Privacy Policy  
  
  |  |   | 

**Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy describes the collection, use, storage and disclosure practices of information collected by DynamicOxygen, LLC. ("DO") that owns and operates [www.dynamicoxygen.com](http://www.dynamicoxygen.com/) and provides online search-advertising solutions (the "Service").

The Service may collect any or all of the following information: (i) non-personally identifiable information (including, without limitation: Cookies, aggregate traffic and usage data, IP address, browser type, ISP, operating system, domain name, date/time stamp, referring/exit website addresses, browsing and search activity) ("Non-PII"), and/or (ii) personally identifiable information (including, without limitation: email address, name, mailing address, phone number and Tax ID) ("PII").

**Non-PII**

DO automatically collects Non-PII that may be used to improve our Service or website. Additionally, Non-PII may be shared with third party vendors, clients, partners and publishers, but only in anonymous form.

Non-PII may be collected from browsers, advertisers and third-party sites via the use of Cookies, log files and web beacons. "Cookies" are files that are stored on your Internet enabled device. Cookies are used to improve the Service. The Service cannot control the use of Cookies or the resulting information collected by advertisers or other third parties. You may set up your browser to deny Cookies; however, please note that Cookies may be required to access certain parts of the Service. .Log Files. contain data such as: IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, click data and types of advertisements viewed. "Web beacons" track: browsing behavior, transaction completion, application submission and the navigation of website(s). All information collected by Cookies, Log files and Web beacons are Non-PII.

**Opt-out of Cookies**

You may opt-out of DO Cookies at [Dynamic Oxygen Opt Out Page](https://member.dynamicoxygen.com/optout.jsp)

**PII**

DO may collect PII from Advertisers and Publishers from forms submitted through our site or use of public areas, such as a blog or forum. Additionally, we receive and store any information you provide via email correspondence, or that you provide in any other way. You may choose to withhold certain information but your use of the Service or website may be limited as a result. Information provided by you is used to properly maintain your account with us, manage invoicing, billing and collections, process payments, comply with all relevant laws and regulations, respond to your inquiries, improve your user experience and communicate with you. DO reserves the right to transfer or assign the information collected from you in whole or in part if it is acquired or merged with another company.

DO reserves the right to disclose your PII as required by law and when DO has a good faith belief that such disclosure is necessary to protect and/or defend the rights of DO and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process. DO may, as permitted by applicable law, disclose your PII to third parties in connection with an investigation of fraud, infringement, piracy, or other unlawful activity and you expressly authorize DO to make such disclosures.

**Third Parties**

The DO Service is used by third-parties such as, Advertisers, Publishers and Network Builders who may automatically collect Non-PII of its users through the Service and may make use of various tools such as cookies or web beacons to improve the performance of their site, ads or user experience. DO is not responsible for the information collection, privacy practices or the content of these third parties. You should check the applicable privacy policies of these third-party advertisers to determine how the information they collect from you is handled.

**Notifications / Announcements / Communications**

You may receive information on products, services, features, and newsletters from the Service and/or third-parties only if you have .opted-in. or signed up to receive such communications through your account, our website, or through any third-party site affiliated with us or our Service. You may .opt-out. by contacting us at the email address listed below or by updating your account settings. You may receive strictly service-related notifications which are non-commercial in nature and do not have an opt-out option. You may email us to opt-out of having your PII shared with third parties at any time. Your email opt-out request should include your full name and email address and be sent to privacy@dynamicoxygen.com.

**Data Security**

DO employs commercially reasonable measures to preserve the integrity and security of your PII. Once we receive your transmission of information, we make commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems. However, please note that there is no guarantee that the transmission of any information is completely secure. A number of factors, including but not limited to unauthorized use, security breach or systems failure, may compromise data security. By transmitting information and/or communicating with us, you hereby acknowledge and agree to assume this risk.

**Privacy of Minors**

No part of the Service is intended for use by any person under the age of 18. The Service does not solicit, knowingly collect or store any information from persons who are under 18 years of age. If you are under 18 years of age, please do not access or use the Service.

**Modifications**

You are encouraged to check this privacy policy for updates as DO reserves the right to change this policy at any time and in its sole and absolute discretion. Any changes will be effective immediately upon posting. Your continued use of the Service and website following the posting of any changes to the policy will constitute acceptance of such changes as well as any future revisions. All information will be used and stored in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

_Last modified on November 30, 2010._

|
